Ooh!
(Emily:)Have you ever been
to an escape room?
Mm-mm, what's that?
Um...
(Emily:)it's kind of like
interactive theater,
(Emily:)except you have
to solve puzzles
(Emily:)in a certain amount
of time to get out.
(Emily:)There's one downtown
where they
(Emily:)trap you in a room
with a zombie.
(short laugh)
Oh!
(Raj:)So, kind of like what's
happening with Penny right now.
"What would constitute
a perfect day for you?"
(Penny:)Uh, well...
(Penny:)I'd probably sleep in,
do a little yoga,
(Penny:)then lie on the beach while
(Penny:)cute cabana boys
brought me drinks and...
(Penny:)probably get a massage
and then cap off the night
(Penny:)with some dancing.
(Sheldon:)That's it?
Yeah, why?
(Sheldon:)You didn't mention Leonard.
(Penny:)He's there.
(Sheldon:)I don't think so.
(stammers)
Leonard can't stand
(Sheldon:)yoga, the beach,
massages or dancing.
(Penny:)Yeah, well,
he brought a book, okay?
(Penny:)What's yours?
Yeah...
(Sheldon:)Uh, I wake up.